<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Journal Panic</title>
    <link>https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Journal Panic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>knowsuchagency@gmail.com (Stephan Fitzpatrick)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>knowsuchagency@gmail.com (Stephan Fitzpatrick)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:45:24 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:45:24 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>knowsuchagency@gmail.com (Stephan Fitzpatrick)</author>
      <guid>https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;software-engineer&#34;&gt;Software Engineer&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;san-francisco-ca&#34;&gt;San Francisco, CA&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Focused, passionate, and technically competent. An excellent communicator; willing and able to engage people at different skill and leadership levels. Experienced in a broad array of disciplines to include; foreign languages, software development, data modeling, performing arts , blogging, fitness, public speaking, and teaching. An active member of the local tech community, helping to plan, organize, and present in local tech events. An avid learner with a voracious appetite for knowledge. Most importantly, a friendly human-being with a genuine desire to help others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;work-experience&#34;&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Developer/Analyst&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jan, 2012 – May, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tasked with providing timely and accurate intelligence to various stakeholders. Granted a unique assignment amongst over 2000 military personnel to be a full-time software developer; working alongside National Security Agency Mathematicians, Computer Scientists, and Engineers, to create new software applications and data pipelines for intelligence analysts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;US NAVY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cryptologic Technician Interpretive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jun, 2010 – May, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intelligence gathering and analysis as a Mandarin Chinese linguist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;DEFENSE LANGUAGE INSTITUTE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree - Mandarin Chinese&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jul, 2010 – Dec, 2011&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graduated 2+/2 from elite military language program with an accredited Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CITY COLLEGE OF SAN FRANCISCO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Transfer - Cognitive Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sep, 2016 – Current&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following are classes I have taken or am currently taking at CCSF prior to transferring to Berkeley for Cognitive Science&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS231 - Advanced Python Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS 110B - C++ Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS 212 - iPhone Programming (Swift)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHIL 12A - Symbolic Logic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHIL 25C - Modern Philosophy through Kant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MATH 100A - Calculus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CS260A/P - Linux System Administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;projects&#34;&gt;PROJECTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOFISH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sole Developer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jun, 2014 – May, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A text parser that has so far processed over four million lines of data and saved analysts over three-thousand man-hours worth of work per year. Written over several months while working as an analyst. Led to a Joint Service Achievement Medal and placement into an official software development role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UNNAMED PROJECT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Developer/ Military-Civilian liason/ SME&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jun, 2014 – May, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A collaborative project between DoD civilian leadership and military personnel designed to store, share, and analyze information for military analysts and their customers. Worked as a project lead, software developer, subject-matter expert, and military-civilian liason. Catalyzed the project by engaging leadership and developers; helping them to understand the problem, define the solution, and validate the necessity of the project and its potential to enable previously unfeasible insight and analytics. Created and implemented the data model for the project using MySQL, MongoDB, Python, SQLAlchemy, and PyMongo. Munged five years worth of semi-formatted text files and used the information to develop the data model and later seed the database. Provided domain knowledge as an analyst and subject-matter expert to the rest of the development team throughout development process.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 23:21:31 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>knowsuchagency@gmail.com (Stephan Fitzpatrick)</author>
      <guid>https://knowsuchagency.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/950C7EY.jpg&#34; width=500&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I&amp;rsquo;m not programming, I&amp;rsquo;m reading, exercising, or volunteering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I served six years in the Navy as a Chinese linguist. During that time, I transitioned from translation work, to intelligence analysis, and finally to software development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-Founder of PyHawaii, Hawaii&amp;rsquo;s Python User Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also been involved in HiCapacity, Code for Hawaii, Code for San Francisco, Data for Democracy, and most recently, Alpha Beta Gamma - CCSF&amp;rsquo;s business honor&amp;rsquo;s society as its inter-council representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to say hello. I love meeting new people :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>